帕梅隆·塔克 你做的这些饼干和肉汁
Pameron Tucker, you outdid yourself
完全超越了自我
on these biscuits and gravy.
太好吃了
They are so tasty,
好吃到想让你打咱妈[俚语]
they make you want to slap your mama.
我说得对吗 米奇尔
Am I right, Mitchell?
当然 如果真有这么个说法 肯定的
Sure. If that's a thing, why not?
愿主保佑
Bless your hearts.
我饱到要炸了[俚语]
I'm fuller than a dog tick.
不要因为他们那么说...
Hey, just because they do it...
这是我的一点小心意
It's the least I could do,
自从你俩为我敞开大门
since you'uns opened your home to me
照顾了我不知道多少星期
for I don't know how many weeks now.
三星期
Three.
我就想不明白了
I just don't get it.
-他怎么能抛下我 -我懂
- How could he leave me? - I know.
我这么漂亮
I'm pretty.
他在床上爱怎么来我都随他
There's nothing I won't let him do in the b-e-d.
亲爱的 你吃了不少哦 是吧
Hey, sweetheart, you're such a big eater, aren't ya, huh?
不敢相信我竟然被抛弃了
I can't believe I got left.
抛弃了
Left!
所以 小帕被抛弃了
So, Pam got left.
她丈夫博趁她在龙卷风后 把转晕了的小猪
Her husband, Bo, took off with half their stuff
赶回猪圈的时候 拿着他们一半的东西走人了
when she was out rounding up dazed piglets after a twister.
我没开玩笑
I'm not kidding.
我坚持让她跟我们住在一起
I insisted she stay with us
这样我可以帮她重树自信
so I could help build up her confidence again.
小帕的自我价值一直以来
Pam's self-worth has always been
都以是否得到男人的注意为准
tied to the attention of men.
这个 你懂的
Which, you know,
让莉莉看到也许不太好吧
maybe isn't the best thing for Lily to witness.
-你在说什么 -没 没什么
- What are you talking about? - N-Nothing.
可能只是我胡思乱想吧
I'm probably just imagining it.
我才没有胡思乱想
I'm not imagining it.
也许是他
It could be him!
可能是他 大家伙儿 可能是他打来了
That could be him, you guys! It could be him!
滚
Get!
可能是他 可能是他
That could be him! It could be him!
不是他
It's not him.
这比我在两年制大学度过的三年里
Wow, this is more reading than I did
读的东西还要多
in my three years at a two-year college.
我想要辣酱热狗
I'm thinking chili dog,
就是我老爸给我买过的那种 愿他安息
just like Pops -- may he rest in peace --
他在我看人生第一场棒球赛时给我买过辣酱热狗
bought me at my first baseball game.
我能说实话[香肠]吗
May I be frank?
我们有熏肠[下体]哦
We have a wiener.
怪怪的但是很贴心
Oh, that's so weirdly sweet.
你的头发纹丝不动好可爱啊
And it's so cute how your hair never moves.
简直像乐高
It's like a LEGO.
我认识你
Hey, I know you!
科切拉音乐节 你还在我的货车上跳舞来着
Coachella, dancing on top of my van.
不是啦 只是我看起来像那种...
No, I just have one of those faces that --
你是海莉吧
It's Haley, right?
海莉 你要介绍我们认识一下吗
Haley, would you like to introduce us?
好吧
Um, okay.
这是我男朋友安迪 这是...
Andy, my boyfriend, this is...
-汤姆 -汤姆
- Tom. - Tom.
汤姆 汤姆
Tom Tom.
你是切罗基人吗
Is that Cherokee?
-我该 -再见
- I should -- - Bye.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我知道你是比我野了点
Hey, I know that you're a little wilder than I am.
这也是我爱上你的原因之一 有点小激动呢
It's one of the reasons I fell for you. It's exciting.
你没必要说这些来安慰我
You don't have to say that.
不 我是认真的
No, I mean it.
这样吧 别吃晚饭看电影了
You know what? Let's forget about dinner and a movie.
我们来干点狂野海莉会做的事情
Let's do what Wild Haley would do instead.
说真的 我已经基本准备
Honestly, I've been kind of ready
要把狂野海莉的派对专用鞋扔掉了
for Wild Haley to chuck her party pumps in the trash.
或者捐给慈善机构 随便啦
Or give them to charity, blah, blah, blah -- whatever.
但如果那是安迪喜欢我的原因之一
But if that's one of the things that Andy liked about me,
我就不会改掉
I wasn't gonna shut it down.
好吧 我们可以先去
Okay, well, we can start
一个西边的酒吧 我认识那里的酒保
at this western place where I know the bartender.
如果你躲起来 我可以弄到一整晚的免费酒喝
If you hang back, I can get us free drinks all night.
不会觉得奇怪吗
It won't look weird,
每次过去你都点两杯酒
you ordering two drinks every time you go up?
不会
No.
那就燥起来吧
Then let's turn this mother out.
我一下子
I got pretty lucky
想到那句话还挺走运的
pulling that expression out of my fanny.
我向来不擅长这种派对
I'm not usually so quick with party talk,
但我总担心
but I've always had this fear
海莉会觉得我跟不上她
that Haley would think I couldn't keep up with her,
所以我只要尽力待上一整晚
so I just tried to survive the night
然后不要吐在我老爸的旧教堂衫上就行
and not barf on my dad's old church shirt.
克莱尔
Claire?
我们能开始看电影了吗
Can we watch the movie now?
-亲爱的 -回答他
- Honey? - Answer him!
亲爱的 拜托 我得把这个提议搞定先
Honey, please. I just have to approve this proposal.
我已经花了一整周时间了
I've been working on it all week.
我的天哪
Oh...my...God.
没错 妈妈的帝国日不落
That's right. Sun never sets on Mama's empire.
不是啦 你还记得我们注册的那个
No, remember the travel app we signed up for
推荐最后一刻折扣的应用吗
that gives you the last-minute deals?
巴黎三晚加头等舱
Three nights in Paris, first-class airfare,
加四星级酒店 几乎等于不用钱啊
four-star hotel for basically nothing.
飞机明天中午就飞了
The flight leaves at noon tomorrow.
我们只有五分钟时间决定
We have five minutes to answer.
等等 你不是真的在考虑吧
Wait. You're not seriously considering this, are you?
简直是世纪大折扣啊
It's kind of the deal of the century.
而且 我们只要请一天假就行了
Plus, we'd only miss one day of work.
海莉跟安迪在一起 卢克去滑雪了
Haley's with Andy. Luke's on a ski trip.
我没关系啊
I don't matter.
亲爱的 我们到那里的时候
Oh, sweetie, by the time we got there,
我们会因为倒时差累死的
we would be so messed up on the time change,
我们只会在恶心的雾里四处乱逛而已
we would just wander around in, like, a nauseous fog.
或者你也可以逼你自己
Or you could just force yourselves
今晚通宵
to stay up all night tonight,
然后明天在飞机上睡觉
then sleep on the plane tomorrow,
这样等你到了巴黎后
and then when you land in Paris,
你过的就是正常的巴黎时间
your morning will be Paris' morning.
听听吧
There we go!
我们太幸运了 还好是最聪明的在家
Lucky for us, the smart one's home.
这主意多好
It's such a sweet idea,
但我这礼拜上班太累了
but I am so tired from work this week.
还有什么比春天的巴黎更能给人动力的吗
What is more energizing than springtime in Paris?
飘香的法棍 有趣的哑剧 相爱的臭鼬
Baguettes baking, mimes miming, skunks in love.
这才是生活
This is what life is.
-这才是生活[法语] 好吗 -不
- C'est la vie, right? - Nope.
不亦乐乎[法语]
Joie de vivre.
好一点
Better.
听我说 有一天我们会老到
Look, someday, watching movies on the couch
只能在沙发上看电影
is the only thing we'll be able to do,
但现在 我们要开一枪
but right now, let's fire a warning shot
警告时间老人
right through Father Time's beard
然后在不朽之城度过一个周末
and spend a weekend in the Eternal City.
那是罗马
Rome.
翡翠城
Emerald City.
西雅图或者绿野仙踪
Seattle or Oz.
她知道我说的是哪里 快没时间了
She knows where I mean, and the clock's running!
你真的想去吗
You really want to do this, don't you?
我们周二回来时就会有终身难忘的回忆
We'd be back Tuesday with the story of a lifetime.
快按下橘色按钮
Press the orange square.
快按下橘色按钮[法语]
Pressez-vous le square orange.
太好了 我们要去啦
Yeah! We're doing it!
抱歉 睡眠先生 你得等等了
Sorry, sleep! You'll have to wait!
我要把时间调到巴黎时间
We're setting our watches to Paris time,
那就是
which is...
比我们早九小时
Nine hours ahead.
好了 现在是晚上九点半 换算过去是
Okay. Okay, it's 9:30 right now...
数学老师哭了 早上六点半
Oh, my God! 6:30.
要多长时间才能卸完妆啊
How long's it take to get the makeup off?
我撤出西贡[越战战场]都比你这快
I got out of Saigon faster.
你喜欢那个女人每天早上出门时的样子
You like what walks out the door every morning,
那就别抱怨过程了
so don't complain about the process.
我车库里有台地板打磨机
I got a floor sander in the garage
如果那样能更快点让我用浴室的话
if it'll open up the bathroom sooner.
有点不方便是吧 杰
Aw, feeling a little put-out, Jay?
这是我的浴室 记得吗
It's my bathroom, remember?
曼尼 那里没痘痘
Manny, there's no pimple there.
是闭口型的 我都能感觉到在跳
It's the underground kind. I can feel my heartbeat in it.
我退休了 需要给自己找点事做
I retired. I needed a little project.
所以我决定装修一下主卧的洗手间
So I decided to redo our master bathroom.
是啊 要是有人警告过你
Yeah, if only someone had told you
这件事比在YouTube上看起来
that it was going to be harder and longer
难多了也费时多了就好了
than it looked on YouTube.
但我警告过你了
Oh, wait!
如果你能按我贴在两个地方的
If you just followed the simple bathroom schedule
英西双语洗手间使用日程来使用
I posted in two places in English and Spanish...
谁会做这种事
Yes, who does that?
谁会给家人发使用日程
Who puts a schedule up for their family?
别进去
Uh, don't go in there.
我要去拿美颜[消失]霜 我找不到了
I need to get my vanishing cream. I can't find it.
挺有效果的
Must've worked.
真搞笑 我忘记
So funny, I forgot to --
淋浴间怎么了
What happened to the shower?!
不是做好了吗
It was finished!
我重做了 我不太喜欢砖缝的样子
I started over. I wasn't loving the grout.
这至少又要花一周
This is gonna take at least one more week.
别弄得自己不开心
Don't upset yourself.
不 是你让我不开心的
No, you are upsetting myself!
今晚你睡沙发
And you're gonna go and sleep on the couch.
你说真的吗
Are you serious?
好吧
Fine.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
里面是刚铺的沥青
That's fresh tar in there.
你想整晚闻着那个味儿睡吗
You really want to smell that all night long?
关于这个洗手间我只做一个决定
I get to make one decision about this bathroom.
把门开着
The door stays open!
好吧
Fine.
洗手间装修给我造成了很多困扰
Um, in all the bathroom confusion,
我吃的好像不是多维片
instead of my multivitamin,
而是避孕药
I may have taken a birth-control pill.
我觉得没事
I think you'll be fine.
反正我今晚也不需要
And anyways, for sure I won't be needing one tonight!
可能是药物作用
It may be the pill,
我现在感觉有点受伤
but I'm feeling a little attacked right now.
火还没灭你就喝了吗
Did you drink that while it was still on fire?
旧习惯了
It's an old habit.
我之前就是这么吃烤棉花糖的
It's how I used to eat my marshmallows.
我喜欢这个男人
I love this guy.
你也好漂亮啊
And you're so pretty.
真高兴认识你们
It's really good meeting you two.
海莉 跟比安卡舌吻我就给你20块
Haley, I'll give you 20 bucks to make out with Bianca.
20块
20 bucks?
比安卡抽烟 我不喜欢
So, Bianca's a smoker. Didn't love that.
她还喜欢乱摸
Or the wandering hands.
不过这些都是"疯狂版海莉"的一部分
But it's all a part of the Wild Haley experience.
天哪
God!
不是吧
No!
12秒 挺不错的
12 seconds! Not bad!
超有意思
And it was so fun.
所以我一直在尖叫
That's why I was screaming.
今晚太棒了
Wow, what a night, huh?
可惜已经这么晚了
Sucks it's so late.
对我们要去的地方来说并不晚
Not where we're going.
我知道你的意思 赌城
I know that look -- Vegas!
来吧 要去吗
Come on! You in?
总的来说
Turtle-y!
我喜欢这主意
I love this idea.
我也是 我还怕今晚就这么结束了
Me too! I was scared we were done.
走吧
Let's go.
我腿有点软
That's some tender meats.
我生气时会睡不着 一直都是
I can't sleep when I'm angry. Never could.
那些能睡着的人一定有问题
And there's something very wrong with people who can.
你这么晚发邮件是想干嘛
What are you doing sending e-mails this time of night?
真的吗
Really?
你想要人陪
You want some company?
歌洛莉亚在适应我更多的存在感
Gloria's just adjusting to me being around more.
我们老是妨碍到对方
We're on top of each other -- and not in a good way.
有意思 我还以为你们的性生活会变好呢
Oh, fun. I was hoping your sex life would come up.
爸 重新装修不容易
Look, Dad, remodels are tense.
我处理的离婚官司一半都是装修引发的
Half the divorces I do start with a remodel.
或者内衣模特[谐音]
Or an underwear model.
你需要点什么吗
Can I get you anything?
-你知道"鲁宾三明治"是什么吗 -知道
- You know what a Reuben is? - Yes.
不 你不知道
No, you don't.
"鲁宾三明治"是这么做的
This is a Reuben.
面包和腌牛肉是分开烤的
You grill the bread and the corned beef separately.
我说的是腌牛肉
Now, I said "corned beef."
就像马提尼里面没有伏特加
There's no vodka in a martini.
鲁宾三明治里也不放熏牛肉
There's no pastrami in a Reuben.
你把它们放到一起
You put 'em together.
然后是德国酸菜 瑞士奶酪和俄式调味酱
Then you have 'kraut, Swiss, Russian.
轴心国 中立国 盟友
Axis, neutral, Ally.
就是这么记得
That's how you remember.
知道了 罗德里格 7号
Got it. Roderigo! Number siete!
今天大家都怎么了
What's with people today?
人就是这样的
Yeah, it's totally people.
爸 你别这么激动
Look, Dad, you get so worked up.
你应该跟我学学
You should try doing this thing that I'm doing
我决定不让任何事情影响我的心情
where I just decide not to let things bother me.
-真的吗 是的
- Really? - Yep.
所以你才半夜一个人来这里吗
That's why you're here alone in the middle of the night?
现在在家工作
It's just a little hard
感觉有点艰难
to get work done at my house right now.
每年一次
So, once a year,
空气中会出现某种花粉
some sort of pollen is released into the air,
所以有两个星期小卡睡觉都会
and for two weeks, Cam has allergy-induced sleep apnea
带着帮助呼吸的仪器以免过敏窒息
and has to use an apparatus in order to help him breathe.
会很丑吗
Is it hideous?
什么很丑
Is what hideous?
我都没注意到有东西
I barely even noticed it.
问题是 小帕有一样的毛病
What's challenging is, Pam has the same condition.
我以为如果能把两人频率调成一致
I thought that maybe I could focus
我应该就能不受影响了
if I could get those contraptions in sync.
你干嘛还要插回去
Why did you plug it back in?
好笑
Charming.
和你不同 我没生气 也没引起争吵
No, unlike you, I didn't engage, and I avoided a fight.
所以我这边一点事都没有
So all is well on my side of the street.
米奇尔 你的键盘上
Mitchell, there's a pile of little orange hairs
掉了一堆红毛
on your keyboard.
你又开始拔眉毛了
You're picking your eyebrows again.
我当年送你去少年棒球队的时候你也这样
Like you did when I put you in Little League.
好吧 我有点压力
Okay, I am a little stressed.
不过都是因为 我工作太多了
But it's just 'cause I'm -- I'm buried under work.
而且小卡的姐姐对莉莉有很大的负面影响
And Cam's sister is the worst influence on Lily.
可我不能吼她 因为她太能哭了
But I-I can't yell at her because she's a sopping mess.
所以我该朝谁吼
So, you know, who am I supposed to yell at?
我那需要机器帮助呼吸的丈夫吗
My husband, who needs a machine to breathe?
你最好找个发泄的途径
Well, you better find yourself an outlet.
所以我喝威士忌打高尔夫抽雪茄
That's why I have scotch and golf and cigars.
不然我一定已经炸了
Otherwise, I'd be a raging jackass.
-我们没有燕麦面包了 -那就去烤
- We're out of rye. - Then bake some!
你能别冲给我们端食物的
Can you please not yell at the woman
女人吼吗
who's bringing us our food?
我们的食物 别说了 太恶心了
I -- our food -- Stop that. That's gross!
桌子像被狐狸踩过一样
It's like a fox ran across the table.
我们走吧
We're out of here.
不 我还得工作
No, I have work to do.
不 你得好好发泄一下
No, you got to blow off some steam.
好吧 感觉跟少年棒球队好像
O-Okay, this sounds a lot like Little League.
我们最好别真去击球笼
We better not be going to a batting cage.
现在千万别往我手里塞棒子
You do not want to put a bat in my hands right now.
说得好像你能打到我一样
Like you could hit me.
走吧
Let's go.
醒醒 我们要去法国了
Out of that trance! We're going to France!
我只是在打哈欠 这都早上2点半了
I can yawn. It's 2:30 in the morning.
不 女士 现在是早上11点半
Mais non, mademoiselle! It's 11:30 in the morning.
辛苦你啦
Thanks for doing these.
好啦
Yeah.
-我说过... -你说过了
- Did I mention that -- - Yes, you did --
如果你睡裤穿得足够低
that if you wear your sweatpants low enough,
今晚我就会看见伦敦和法国
tonight, I will see London, I will see France,
然后 我就看到你的内裤了
and then, yes, I will see your underpants.
菲尔
Phil!
你睡着了
You're asleep!
不 不 不
Oh, no, no, no!
没问题 我们可以小睡一下
It's fine. We can take a nap.
欧洲人经常打瞌睡
Europeans are always napping.
好吧 没什么比做这个更糟了
Actually, that's the worst thing you can do.
她说的没错 克莱尔 振作点
She's right, Claire. Get up.
你为什么还醒着
Why are you still awake?
太兴奋睡不着了
I'm too excited to sleep.
我在学习大爆炸核聚变的...
I'm studying Big Bang nucleosynthesis --
更确切地说
well, more specifically
是宇宙中的重子物质总量
the total Baryonic matter in the universe.
言归正传
Let's go back.
暗物质和暗能量的比重
Dark matter and dark energy
占所有物质的95%
make up 95% of all of the matter in the --
-不 走开 -别念了
- No! Go away! - Stop!
我们需要帮助
We needed help.
如何保持清醒网站上第一条毫无疑问就是
And no surprise, first entry on howtostayawake.net --
咖啡
coffee.
-果然有用 -要的就这效果
- This did it. - This is all we needed.
-来帮我按按脚吧 -那你也按按我的
- You want to rub my feet? - If you rub mine.
菲尔
Phil!
脚 我们为什么要按脚
The feet! Why'd we do the feet?!
第二条 保持运动状态
Second tip -- stay active.
你才睡着了呢
You're asleep!
最后我们终于找了有效的方法
Finally, we found something that worked.
对我有效
For me.
不 搞什么鬼
No! What the hell?!
我的亲娘啊
Oh, my nana!
我们去溜达一下找点东西吃怎么样
What do you say we take a walk and get something to eat?
现在是法国的午餐时间
It is French lunchtime.
好啊 值得一试
Sure. It's worth a shot.
走之前我还有点事
Got to do something first.
搞什么
Why?!
干吗乱吓人
Why would you do that?!
我的意思就是
Alls I'm saying is,
如果能幸运地遇到你喜欢的这个莱恩
if you're lucky enough to get this boy Ryan you like,
就要好好把握
you hold on with both hands.
他一旦离开 你就什么都不是了
'Cause once he's gone, you're nothing.
好吧 你不是这个意思
Okay, you don't really mean that.
我也不知道我什么意思
I don't know what I mean.
我只是满嘴跑火车而已
I'm just a woman running her fool mouth off.
这些自我主导的信息跟我们想教给
Okay, not exactly the message of empowerment
21世纪生的女儿的不一样
we'd like to impart to our 21st-century daughter.
杜冷丁针剂是什么
What's a Demerol shooter?
好了 我说 咱们声音小点
Okay, you know what? Let's keep our voices down.
我可不想把别人吵醒证明谁是对的
We don't want anyone woken up and proven correct.
给我
Give me that.
-再抽一口 -不行 别抽了
- One more drag! - No. Stop.
它能把我怎么样 害死我吗
What's the worst it's gonna do? Kill me?
别抽了
Stop...it!
那根是我卷的
Hey, I rolled that!
妈妈
Mama!
干吗
What?!
对不起 对不起 是你啊 宝贝
Sorry, sorry. It's you, Papi.
怎么了
What's wrong?
能不能拜托你去看看乔
Can you please deal with Joe?
再去看看治疗师
And also get a therapist?
妈妈
Mama!
声音不是从他卧室传来的
That is not coming from his bedroom.
妈妈
Mama!
哦不
Oh, no!
我刚才想喝水 然后就被粘在这了
I wanted a glass of water, and I got stuck.
真该死
Damn it!
我怎么不关门呢 关了你就不会
Why didn't I close that door so you didn't get stuck
像曼尼的沙鼠那样被粘住了
like Manny's gerbil in the glue trap?!
可你说它逃走了
But you said he ran away.
是啊 它的大部分是逃走了
Yes, most of him did.
把鞋脱了
Take off your slippers.
对 好主意
Oh, yeah, good idea.
可别把鞋弄脏
Don't want anything bad to happen to them.
好的
Okay.
等等 你这是干什么
Wait! What are you doing?!
你疯了吗 这皮是佛罗伦萨的
Are you crazy?! They're Florentine leather!
曼尼 我们只是说说而已
Ay, Manny, that's what we just told you.
这在中国城买的
We got them in Chinatown.
好了 小小乔
Okay, Little Joe.
这就把你弄起来
Let's get you out of there.
起来
Okay, come on!
好了 好了
Okay. Ay.
我们得把睡衣
Now we're gonna burn these pajamas
跟毛巾 拖鞋一起烧了
with the towel and the slippers.
烧了
Burn them?
我的头发也粘到了
It's in my hair, too.
我来剪
Okay. I will cut it.
去 跑去把剪刀拿给妈妈
Go. Grab some scissors and run them back to Mama.
我去拿剪刀吧 乔
I'll get the scissors, Joe!
其实那沙鼠我都不想要
I didn't even want him,
我是唯一确保它活着的人
and I'm the only one keeping him alive.
好了 得把这个弄平整
Okay, I just have to smooth this out
杰就什么都不会发现了
so that Jay doesn't notice anything.
为了瞒他
You're really going through
你真是大费周章
a lot of trouble to hide this from him.
你不明白
You just don't understand.
这次吵架是有史以来
This is the first time in a fight
第一次我全对 杰全错的
that I was 100% right and Jay was 100% wrong.
以前从未有过
That never happens.
全对有那么重要吗
And being right is so important?
先结婚再跟老娘说话
Get married and then get back to me.
不 卡住了 过来帮我一把
Ay, no! This is stuck! Come help me!
推
Push!
哦不 我的生日礼物劳力士
Oh, no! My birthday Rolex!
想多了 曼尼
Ay, Manny.
麻烦结账
We'll take the check, please.
不
No!
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
我超想睡的 菲尔
I want to go to sleep so bad, Phil.
也许这个能让你醒着
Maybe this will keep you awake.
我们家不可能这么远
Our house cannot be this far.
我们已经走了
We've been walking for...
我们已经走过这个床垫了
We've passed this mattress already.
这就是命
It's fate.
上帝想让我睡觉
God wants me to sleep.
坚持住 坚持住 克莱尔
Fight it! Fight it, Claire!
放开我
Let me go!
不行 不行 我们离目标很近了
No! No! We're so close!
我不能让你放弃
I can't let you quit!
天 我才不会在那么脏的垫子上睡...
Oh, God. I'm not gonna go to sleep on some filthy mattress...
好吧
Okay.
太久
for long.
不 不
No. No!
对不起
No, no. I'm sorry.
我上班已经很累了
I'm so tired from work already.
我在巴黎玩不起来的
I won't be any fun in Paris.
你去吧
You should go.
泡个妞 我不在乎
Meet someone. I don't care.
我真的做不到 对不起
I just can't do it. I'm sorry.
我们还是不去了吧
You know what? Let's not.
我不该逼你
I shouldn't have pushed you.
我知道我说了不想变老之类的话
I know I said all that stuff about not wanting to get old,
可是
but...
我那么想去是因为我想你
I think I really wanted to go because I miss you.
因为我工作太忙了吗
Because I've been working so much?
是啊 忙挺好的
Yeah, which is great.
我也希望你能充实自己
I-I really want that for you.
我觉得我
I-I think I...
我只想来场冒险
I just wanted a little adventure.
可你知道吗
But you know what?
我们今晚已经很欢乐了
We've had so much fun tonight.
我上次跟你
When was the last time
熬夜到凌晨五点是什么时候
I got to stay up until 5:00 in the morning with you?
把手给我
Give me that hand.
要做什么
What for?
这一掌是为了让我清醒
That's to wake me up.
这一掌是为惩罚我
And that is for ever forgetting
忘了你是最棒的老公
that you are the best husband.
这是干吗
Oh. What's that for?
拍死爬到我身上的东西
For whatever's crawling all over me!
哦不 也爬到我身上了
Oh, no! They're on me, too!
一小时40块 歌都在单子里
$40 for the hour. Songs are in the book.
有人要鸡尾酒吗
Anyone want a cocktail?
-你知道怎么调曼哈顿吗 -知道
- You know how to make a Manhattan? - Yes.
你不知道 曼哈顿只有...
No, you don't. The only Manhattan --
他知道了 爸
He's got it, Dad.
谢谢 谢了
Thank you. Thanks.
K歌厅
So, a karaoke bar, huh?
你认为唱流行歌曲就能
You know, it's a little offensive that you think
解决我的问题挺伤人的
singing a pop song is gonna solve my problems.
你是认为我有多基
How gay do you think I am?
米奇尔
Mitchell!
麦当娜
Madonna!
好吧 好吧
Oh! Yeah. Okay.
来吧
Well, come on!
你小时候很紧张的时候
When you were stressed out as a kid,
你会在客厅唱麦当娜的歌跳她的舞
you used to dance and sing Madonna in the living room.
你马上就好了
Fixed you right up.
我一点都不惊讶
Ah, I'm not surprised.
你觉得我在过去25年里一点都没变
You think I haven't changed at all in 25 years.
如果你真的感到惊讶 我就不会知道了
If you were surprised, I wouldn't know it,
因为你一直在拔眉毛
since you've plucked out all your eyebrows.
麦当娜 米奇尔
Madonna, Mitchell.
告诉你吧 我不会唱的
News flash -- I am not singing.
告诉你吧 你会的
News flash -- yes, you are!
你知道吗 爸
You know what, Dad?
你今晚真的很霸道
You have been really bossy tonight.
对我 对那个服务员
With me, with that waitress.
我猜就是这样你才会和歌洛莉亚有矛盾
I-I bet that's why you and Gloria are having problems.
是的
Yeah.
你怀念在工作中指挥别人
You miss bossing people around at work,
所以现在你就在家这么做
so now you're doing it at home.
如果我承认你说的有那么一点点对
If I admitted there was some truth in that,
你能别硬撑着了吗
could you just give in?
你现在摇来摇去就像萝拉·法拉娜一样
You've been grinding around like Lola Falana.
我不知道为什么这对你来说这么重要
I don't know why this is so important to you.
你能不能让我帮你
Can you just let me help you?!
好吧 我会唱的
Okay, I'm doing this,
但只是因为你需要我这么做
but only because you need it so much.
来吧 女孩
Come on, girls!
你们相信爱吗
Do you believe in love?
因为我对此有话要说
'Cause I got something to say about it.
它是这样的东西
And it goes something like this.
*不要退而求其次 宝贝*
*Don't go for second best, baby*
*让你的爱接受考验*
*Put your love to the test*
*你知道 你知道*
*You know, you know...*
看着米奇尔 解决了他的问题
Watching Mitchell, I did feel kind of good
我确实感觉良好
about fixing his problem.
现在退休了 你并不总能觉得自己有用
Now, being retired, you don't always feel useful anymore.
也许这就是我要拆那间浴室的原因
It's probably why I keep tearing up that bathroom.
我猜向歌洛莉亚坦白承认也不是什么坏事
I guess it wouldn't be the worst thing to admit to Gloria.
也许时间久了就会被淡忘的
Eh, it'll probably blow over.
*表达你自己*
*Express yourself*
我去
Damn it.
*表达你自己*
*Express yourself*
我就知道你会辗转反侧睡不着
I knew you'd be up, tossing and turning.
是的 是的
Yes, yes.
为什么你要在沙发上打电话给我
Why are you calling from the couch?
我不在家 说来话长
Not home. Long story.
我要坦白
Look, let me get this out.
我对那间浴室的事是有点过分
I have been going crazy with the bathroom,
但这不真的是因为浴室的原因
but it's not really about the bathroom.
是因为我不再知道我自己是谁了
It's about me not being sure who I am anymore.
你完全没错
You were 100% right.
很高兴听你这么说 但...
I love to hear that, but...
不 你是对的
No, you were.
好吧 别急着回来
Okay. No rush getting home.
我们都很好
We're fine here.
给力 给力 黑
Please, please, please! Come on, black!
红18号
18 red.
就差一点
So close.
赌博最好玩了
Gambling is the best!
你把自己辛苦挣来的钱给陌生人
You hand your hard-earned money to strangers
祈祷能挣回来
and pray it comes back.
我知道我喝了不少
I know I've had a lot to drink,
但那已经不是比安卡了 对吗
but that is not Bianca anymore, is it?
是的
Nope.
克林特不会把她卖了吧
I don't want to believe Clint sold her...
你们想要彻底疯狂起来吗
You guys want to get really crazy?
大家都知道我在哪里
People know where I am.
全押在一个数字上
All-in on one number.
好吧 我想再也没有
Okay, I guess that's no scarier
比那条荧光棒在我嘴里炸开更恐怖的事了
than when that glow-stick broke in my mouth.
去吧
Do it.
安迪 那是一个月的租金啊
Andy, that's, like, a month's rent.
要玩就玩大的不然...
Hey, you got to go big or...
等一下 黑色不是一美金的吗
Wait -- the black ones aren't $1s?
真的吗 好吧 我能不能...
Really? Okay, could I just...
对不起先生 球已经在转了
Sorry, sir. The ball's rolling.
我的天啊
Oh, my gosh.
安迪 你究竟怎么了
Andy, what is happening with you?
为什么你要这么做
Why are you doing this?
你在说什么 我以为你喜欢狂野版的安迪
What are you talking about? I thought you loved Wild Andy.
不 不
No, no.
我喜欢正常版的安迪
I love Normal Andy,
番茄汤和奶酪三明治的安迪
tomato-soup-and-grilled-cheese Andy.
11点上床睡觉的安迪
Still-in-bed-by-11:00 Andy.
喜欢说"小肚肚"的安迪
Uses-the-word-"Tummy" Andy.
真的吗 我这么做
Really? Because I've been doing this whole thing
全是因为我怕如果我没跟上你的节奏
because I was afraid you'd get bored and dump me
你会觉得无聊然后甩了我
if I couldn't keep up.
我知道你无法跟上我的节奏 但我愿意慢下来
I know you can't keep up. But I'd rather slow down.
我喜欢跟你在一起时的我
I like the me I am when I'm with you.
我真希望你能在一分钟前告诉我
Well, I wish you would have told me that about a minute ago.
我不敢看
I can't watch!
压力在我的小肚肚里翻腾
The stress is murder on my tummy.
小帕阿姨要走了
Aunt Pam's leaving.
帕梅隆·杰西卡·塔克 你是想去哪里
Pameron Jessica Tucker, where do you think you're going?
回家 跪在博的面前 求他回心转意
Home -- to get down on my knees and beg Bo to come back.
我会撒谎告诉他我怀孕了
I'm just gonna lie and tell him I'm pregnant.
不 那不是成熟的大人处理事情的方式
No, that is not how mature people handle their problems.
我会跟你决斗的
I will fight you.
你不能回去向那个男人低头
You are not going to crawl back to that man.
你没有话语权 你知道我能打败你
You don't have a choice. You know I can take you.
是吗
Oh, yeah, right.
帕梅隆 不
Pameron -- No!
好吧 你知道吗
Okay, you know what?
你会后悔这么做的
You are going to regret that!
你惹毛我了
Oh, now you poked the bear!
来吧 熊妈妈
Well, come on, Mama Bear!
我来了
I'm coming!
反正这都是我的错
It's all my fault anyway!
是我让他走的
I pushed him away!
因为我从不听他说
Because I never listened!
你真的想让莉莉以为女人都是脆弱的吗
You really want Lily to think women are weak?!
离我大爸远点
Get off my daddy!
你就因为一个男生变得这么疯狂吗
You're acting this crazy all over a boy?!
莉莉 很高兴能听到你这么说
Oh, Lily, I'm so happy to hear you say that!
快拉开帕梅隆阿姨的胸罩扣
Now, pull Aunt Pameron's bra strap!
好吧 我们移开了沙发
Okay. So we moved the couch.
你去哪里了
Where were you?
我 我有些工作要做
I, uh, I had some work to do.
我也是 我要找回我的男人
Me too. Get my man back.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay. All right.
虽然我真的很想不管
As much as I'd love to leave this alone,
但我今晚学到了一些东西
I learned something tonight
我觉得我要分享给你听
that I feel like I-I need to share with you.
你值得得到生命中最好的事物
You deserve the best in life.
所以如果时机不对 那就转身离开吧
So if the time isn't right, then...move on.
退而求其次 这...
Second best, it's...
这配不上你
It's never enough.
你自己会过得更好 宝贝[麦当娜歌词]
You'll do much better, baby, on your own.
宝贝
Baby.
你自己
On your own.
我的天啊
My God.
你说得对
You're right.
是的
Yeah.
不要退而求其次
Don't go for second best.
-让你的爱... -没事 我解决了
- Put your love... - It's okay. I fixed her.
是麦当娜解决了
Madonna fixed her.
别担心 我们有钱的
Don't worry. We've got this.
慢慢来
Take all the time you need.
我只不过是要结束一次12小时的轮班而已
I'm only finishing a 12-hour shift.
你有五美分或十美分什么的吗
Do you got a nickel or a dime or anything?
没有
I don't.
对不起 那么...
Sorry, but...
你可能就要找我零钱了
you're gonna have to make change.
什么
What?!
我爸妈要去巴黎了
My mom and dad are going to Paris.
好吧 通知了孩子 拿好了护照
Okay, children informed, passports secured,
收拾好了行李
luggage packed.
我忘了什么
What am I forgetting?
对了
Oh, yeah.
再会[法语] 艾丽克斯
Au revoir, Alex!
下一站 天堂之城
Next stop, Paradise City.
那是枪炮与玫瑰的歌
Guns and Roses.